Guide to the Archives of Irish America Newspapers and Periodicals Collection AIA.004
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- I: Newspapers, 1836-2018
  - United Irishman (Dublin), 1955–1961; cuid14765 (Box 149)
  - United Irishman (Dublin), Aug 1971-May 1972; cuid14766 (Box 149)
- II: Periodicals, 1881-2008
  - Ais Eiri: The Magazine of Irish-America, 1979-1981; cuid14767 (Box 160, Folder 1A)
  - American Committee for Irish Studies, 1963-1964, 1966-1968, 1970; cuid14768 (Box 160, Folder 1)
  - American Committee for Irish Studies, 1971-1976; cuid14769 (Box 160, Folder 2)
  - American Committee for Irish Studies, 1977-1979; cuid14770 (Box 160, Folder 3)
  - American Gael, 1992-1999; cuid14771 (Box 160, Folder 4)
  - American Irish Newsletter American Irish Political Education Committee, 1993-1997; cuid14772 (Box 160, Folder 5)
  - American Irish Newsletter American Irish Political Education Committee, 1998-1999; cuid14773 (Box 160, Folder 5A)
  - American Irish Newsletter American Irish Political Education Committee, Feb 2000-Jul 2000; cuid14774 (Box 160, Folder 5B)
  - American Journal of Gaelic Culture (Chicago), 1996-1997; cuid14775 (Box 160, Folder 6)
  - An Claidheamh Soulis, Inc. - Newsletter - Litir Nuacht, 1971-1977; cuid14776 (Box 160, Folder 6)
  - An Claidheamh Soluis, Inc. - Sword of Light,The Irish American Review, 1974; cuid14777 (Box 160, Folder 7)
  - An Claidheamh Soluis, Inc.- Ais-Eiri The Magazine of Irish America, Win 1979-Spr 1982; cuid14778 (Box 160, Folder 8)
  - An Claidheamh Soluis, Inc. - An Gael, 1982-1983; cuid14779 (Box 160, Folder 9)
  - An Claidheamh Soluis, Inc. - An Gael, 1984-1985; cuid14780 (Box 160, Folder 10)
  - An Claidheamh Soluis, Inc. - An Gael, 1986; cuid14781 (Box 160, Folder 11)
  - An Claidheamh Soluis, Inc. - An Gael, 1987; cuid14782 (Box 160, Folder 12)
  - An Claidheamh Soluis, Inc. - An Gael, 1990-1992; cuid14783 (Box 160, Folder 13)
  - An Doras, 1996-1998; cuid14784 (Box 160, Folder 14)
  - An Gaodhal, 1881, 1886-1889; cuid14785 (Box 166, Folder 10)
  - An Gaodhal, 1890; cuid14786 (Box 166, Folder 11)
  - An Gaodhal, 1891, 1893-1894; cuid14787 (Box 166, Folder 12)
  - An Gaodhal, 1893-1894 (Box 219, Folder 1)
  - An Gaodhal, 1896; cuid14788 (Box 166, Folder 13)
  - An Gaodhal, 1897-1899; cuid14789 (Box 166, Folder 14)
  - An Gaodhal, 1901 (Box 219, Folder 2)
  - An Gaodhal, 1900-1902; cuid14790 (Box 166, Folder 15)
  - Bard, The, 1996-1999; cuid14791 (Box 160, Folder 15)
  - Beyond Ben Bulben (Australia), 1996-1997; cuid14792 (Box 160, Folder 16)
  - Bonded Shores, 1994-2000; cuid14793 (Box 160, Folder 17)
  - The Bridge: An Droichead, 1986-1987; cuid14794 (Box 160, Folder 18)
  - Callahan's Irish Quarterly, 1977-1981; cuid14795 (Box 160, Folder 19)
  - Callahan's Irish Quarterly, 1982-2008; cuid14796 (Box 160, Folder 20)
  - Carn: A Link Between Celtic Nations, 1974-1978; cuid14797 (Box 160, Folder 21)
  - Celtic News Service, 1975-1977, 1992-1996; cuid14798 (Box 160, Folder 22)
  - Celtic Renewal, 1995; cuid14799 (Box 160, Folder 23)
  - Cois na Farraige, 1984; cuid14800 (Box 160, Folder 24)
  - Desert Shamrock, 1994; cuid14801 (Box 160, Folder 25)
  - Ducas, 1971-1981 with gaps; cuid14802 (Box 161, Folder 26)
  - Ducas, 1985-2002; cuid14803 (Box 161, Folder 27)
  - Eire Ireland, 1963-1968; cuid14804 (Box 161, Folder 1)
  - Eire Ireland, 1969-1973; cuid14805 (Box 161, Folder 2)
  - Everyman, 1994-1995; cuid14806 (Box 161, Folder 3)
  - Gaelic Journal, 1900; cuid14807 (Box 161, Folder 4)
  - Gander, 1993-1997; cuid14808 (Box 161, Folder 5)
  - Gander, 1998-1999; cuid14809 (Box 161, Folder 6)
  - Gander, 1999-2001, 2002, 2004; cuid14810 (Box 161, Folder 7)
  - Harp: "Voice of the Irish Impression", Jun 1988; cuid14811 (Box 161, Folder 8)
  - Here's Me Bus!, 1995-1996; cuid14812 (Box 161, Folder 9)
  - Hibernian Life (Minneapolis, MN): vol. ii, no. 3, Jul-Sep 1989; cuid14813 (Box 166, Folder 16)
  - Holy Cross Quarterl y: The Irish Issue, Vol. 6, Nos. 1-4. College of the Holy Cross, Worcester, MA., 1974; cuid14814 (Box 161, Folder 9A)
  - Hornpipe: Irish Dance, Music and Culture in North America, 1999; cuid14815 (Box 161, Folder 10)
  - Inside Ireland, 1984, 1999; cuid14816 (Box 161, Folder 11)
  - Ireland of the Welcomes, Mar 1966-Mar 1978; cuid14817 (Box 161, Folder 12)
  - Ireland of the Welcomes, 1984; cuid14818 (Box 161, Folder 13)
  - Ireland of the Welcomes, 1985; cuid14819 (Box 161, Folder 14)
  - Ireland of the Welcomes, 1986; cuid14820 (Box 161, Folder 15)
  - Ireland of the Welcomes, 1987; cuid14821 (Box 161, Folder 16)
  - Ireland of the Welcomes, 1988; cuid14822 (Box 161, Folder 17)
  - Ireland of the Welcomes, 1989; cuid14823 (Box 161, Folder 18)
  - Ireland of the Welcomes, 1990; cuid14824 (Box 161, Folder 19)
  - Ireland of the Welcomes, 1991; cuid14825 (Box 162, Folder 20)
  - Ireland of the Welcomes, 1992; cuid14826 (Box 162, Folder 21)
  - Ireland of the Welcomes, 1993; cuid14827 (Box 162, Folder 22)
  - Ireland of the Welcomes, 1994; cuid14828 (Box 162, Folder 23)
  - Ireland of the Welcomes, 1995; cuid14829 (Box 162, Folder 1)
  - Ireland of the Welcomes, 1996; cuid14830 (Box 162, Folder 2)
  - Ireland of the Welcomes, 1997-1998; cuid14831 (Box 162, Folder 3)
  - Ireland of the Welcomes, 1999; cuid14832 (Box 162, Folder 4)
  - Ireland of the Welcomes, 2000-2001; cuid14833 (Box 162, Folder 5)
  - Irish America, 1985, undated; cuid14834 (Box 162, Folder 6)
  - Irish America, Jan 1986-Apr 1986; cuid14835 (Box 162, Folder 7)
  - Irish America, May 1986-Dec 1986; cuid14836 (Box 162, Folder 8)
  - Irish America, 1987; cuid14837 (Box 162, Folder 9, Box Shared Tamiment 018, Folder 21)
  - Irish America, 1988; cuid14838 (Box 162, Folder 10)
  - Irish America, 1989; cuid14839 (Box 162, Folder 11)
  - Irish America, 1990; cuid14840 (Box 162, Folder 12)
  - Irish America, 1991; cuid14841 (Box 163, Folder 13)
  - Irish America, 1992; cuid14842 (Box 163, Folder 14)
  - Irish America, 1993; cuid14843 (Box 163, Folder 1)
  - Irish America, Jan 1994-Jun 1994; cuid14844 (Box 163, Folder 2)
  - Irish America, Jan 1994-Aug 1994; cuid14845 (Box 163, Folder 3)
  - Irish America, Jan 1995-Aug 1995; cuid14846 (Box 163, Folder 4)
  - Irish America, Sep 1995-Dec 1995; cuid14847 (Box 163, Folder 5)
  - Irish America, Jan 1996-Apr 1996; cuid14848 (Box 163, Folder 6)
  - Irish America, May 1996-Dec 1996; cuid14849 (Box 163, Folder 7)
  - Irish America, 1997; cuid14850 (Box 163, Folder 8)
  - Irish America, Mar 1998-Aug 1998; cuid14851 (Box 163, Folder 9)
  - Irish America, Sep 1998-Dec 1998; cuid14852 (Box 163, Folder 10)
  - Irish America, Feb 1999-Jul 1999; cuid14853 (Box 163, Folder 11)
  - Irish America, Aug 1999-Nov 1999; cuid14854 (Box 163, Folder 12)
  - Irish America, Jan 2000-Mar 2000; cuid14855 (Box 163, Folder 13)
  - Irish America, May 2000; cuid14856 (Box 163, Folder 14)
  - Irish America, Aug 2000-Nov 2000; cuid14857 (Box 163, Folder 15)
  - Irish America, Dec 2000-May 2001; cuid14858 (Box 164, Folder 16)
  - Irish America, Jun 2001-Nov 2001; cuid14859 (Box 164, Folder 17)
  - Irish America, Feb 2002-Nov 2002; cuid14860 (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - Irish America, Jan 2003-Nov 2003; cuid14861 (Box 164, Folder 2)
  - Irish America, Jan 2004-May 2004; cuid14862 (Box 164, Folder 3)
  - Irish America, Jun 2004-Sep 2004; cuid14863 (Box 164, Folder 4)
  - Irish America, Jan 2005-Jul 2005; cuid14864 (Box 164, Folder 5)
  - Irish America, Dec 2010-Jan 2011; cuid14865 (Box 164, Folder 5A)
  - Irish American Post Magazine, 1997; cuid14866 (Box 164, Folder 6)
  - Irish American Voice, 1984; cuid14867 (Box 164, Folder 7)
  - Irish American Voice, 1985; cuid14868 (Box 164, Folder 8)
  - Irish American Voice, 1986; cuid14869 (Box 164, Folder 9)
  - Irish American Voice, 1987; cuid14870 (Box 164, Folder 10)
  - Irish at Home and Abroad, 1993-1995; cuid14871 (Box 164, Folder 11)
  - Irish Connections, 2001; cuid14919 (Box Shared Tamiment 018, Folder 21)
  - Irish Dancer, 1998; cuid14872 (Box 164, Folder 12)
  - IE: A Supplement to the Irish Echo, 1996-1998; cuid14873 (Box 164, Folder 13)
  - Irish People (Chicago) Vol. 1, nos. 5-6, 8-12; Vol 2. nos. 5,9,11; Vol 3. no. 1 (also available on microfilm in Tamiment), Oct 1923-Jan 1933 with gaps; cuid14874 (Box 164, Folder 14)
  - The Irish Republican Guard: Issues 3-5, 2009; cuid14875 (Box 166, Folder 17)
  - The Irish Review, 1937; cuid14920 (Box Shared Tamiment 018, Folder 21)
  - Irish Voice Magazine, 1954; cuid14876 (Box 164, Folder 15)
  - Irish Volunteer, 1991, 2000; cuid14877 (Box 164, Folder 16)
  - Keltoi: A Pan-Celtic Review, 1986-1987, 1990; cuid14878 (Box 164, Folder 17)
  - Lies of Our Times: British Terror in Northern Ireland, Oct 1990; cuid14879 (Box 164, Folder 18)
  - Nation, The (Ho Ho Kus, NJ), 1985-1989; cuid14880 (Box 164, Folder 19)
  - Nation, The (Ho Ho Kus, NJ), 1990; cuid14881 (Box 164, Folder 20)
  - Nation, The (Ho Ho Kus, NJ), 1991; cuid14882 (Box 165, Folder 1)
  - Nation, The (Ho Ho Kus, NJ), 1992; cuid14883 (Box 165, Folder 2)
  - Nation, The (Ho Ho Kus, NJ), 1993; cuid14884 (Box 165, Folder 3)
  - Nation, The (Ho Ho Kus, NJ), 1994; cuid14885 (Box 165, Folder 4)
  - Nation, The (Ho Ho Kus, NJ), 1995; cuid14886 (Box 165, Folder 5)
  - Nua Eabhrac, 1981-1981; cuid14887 (Box 165, Folder 6)
  - The Recorder: Bulletin of the American Irish Historical Society. (New York), 1932-1970, 1988; cuid14888; Holdings: 1932, Vol, 5, no. 5; 1933, Vol. 6, nos. 2-4; 1934, Vol. 7, nos. 1-3; 1935 Vol. 8, no. 1; 1936 Vol. 9, nos. 1-4; 1939 Vol. 10, no. 1-2, 6; 1950, Vol. 12, no. 1; 1951 Vol. 13, no. 1; 1952, Vol. 14; 1953 Vol. 15; 1954, Vol. 16; 1955 Vol. 16; 1963, Vol. 24; 1964, Vol. 26; 1965, Vol. 28; 1966, Vol. 29; 1967, Vol. 30; 1968, VOl. 31; 1970. Vol. 33; Supplesment to 1988 "In Memoriam Darcy O'Brien;" List of Publications, 1898-1943 [from 1952 on it looks like only one bulletin was published per annum] (Box 167)
    Scope and Content Note
    Holdings: 1932, Vol, 5, no. 5; 1933, Vol. 6, nos. 2-4; 1934, Vol. 7, nos. 1-3; 1935 Vol. 8, no. 1; 1936 Vol. 9, nos. 1-4; 1939 Vol. 10, no. 1-2, 6; 1950, Vol. 12, no. 1; 1951 Vol. 13, no. 1; 1952, Vol. 14; 1953 Vol. 15; 1954, Vol. 16; 1955 Vol. 16; 1963, Vol. 24; 1964, Vol. 26; 1965, Vol. 28; 1966, Vol. 29; 1967, Vol. 30; 1968, VOl. 31; 1970. Vol. 33; Supplesment to 1988 "In Memoriam Darcy O'Brien;" List of Publications, 1898-1943 [from 1952 on it looks like only one bulletin was published per annum]
  - Republican Bulletin / Iris na Poblachta (Dublin) Vol. 1, nos. 1-3, 1987; cuid14889 (Box 165, Folder 7)
  - Saoirse': Irish Freedom, 1987-1997; cuid14890 (Box 165, Folder 8)
  - Shamrock Leaf, 1990-1996; cuid14891 (Box 165, Folder 9)
  - Shanachie, The, 1990-2000; cuid14892 (Box 165, Folder 10)
  - Spirit of Freedom, 1986-1987; cuid14893 (Box 165, Folder 11)
  - Spirit of Freedom, 1988; cuid14894 (Box 165, Folder 12)
  - Spirit of Freedom, 1989; cuid14895 (Box 165, Folder 13)
  - University College Dublin Alumni Newsletter, Jun 1989-Jan 1993; cuid14896 (Box 165, Folder 14)
  - University College Dublin Alumni Magazine, 1993-1994; cuid14897 (Box 165, Folder 15)
  - University College Dublin Alumni Magazine, 1995-2000; cuid14898 (Box 165, Folder 16)
  - World of Hibernia, 1995; cuid14899 (Box 165, Folder 17)
  - World of Hibernia, 1995-1996; cuid14900 (Box 165, Folder 18)
  - World of Hibernia, 1996; cuid14901 (Box 165, Folder 19)
  - World of Hibernia, 1996-1997; cuid14902 (Box 165, Folder 20)
  - World of Hibernia, 1997; cuid14903 (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - World of Hibernia, Spr 1998; cuid14904 (Box 166, Folder 2)
  - World of Hibernia, Sum 1998-Aut 1998; cuid14905 (Box 166, Folder 3)
  - World of Hibernia, 1998-1999; cuid14906 (Box 166, Folder 4)
  - World of Hibernia, 1999; cuid14907 (Box 166, Folder 5)
  - World of Hibernia, Spr 2000; cuid14908 (Box 166, Folder 6)
  - World of Hibernia, Sum 2000-Win 2000; cuid14909 (Box 166, Folder 7)
  - World of Hibernia, Spr 2001; cuid14910 (Box 166, Folder 8)
  - World of Hibernia, Win 2001; cuid14911 (Box 166, Folder 9)